ANS Record Group 1: Administrative, 1853-ongoing
American Numismatic Society
- Series: General correspondence, 1853 - 2099; 133 cubic feet
  - Box 1.6.4 #25 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Dallin, Cyrus E.; Daly, Bernard A., public stenographer; Daneu & Co. (Palermo, Italy); George Damon & Sons; Darcy & Rogers; Dattari, Giovanni; Davies, J. Clarence; Davis, Gherardi; Davis, R. E. (Mrs.) (Librarian, Chicago Coin Club); Davis, Solomon; Joseph K. Davison’s Sons, manufacturing jewelers; Dawley, Eliza; Dawson’s Book Shop; Day, Arthur P.; Deacon, James H.; Deats, Hiram E.; DeBaum, J. A.; de Bethune, G. (1924 Foreign Medal Exhibition); de Ciccio, Guiseppe.; de Forest, Robert W.; de Francisci, Anthony; de Fuentes, E. Sanchez (Sociedad Nacional Cubana de la Crus Roja); Walter de Gruyter & Co.; De Haan, Roland; De Hart, Arthur; de Heredia, Carlos (Mrs.); Deighton, Bell & Co., Ltd.; de Kay Charles; Delafield, John Ross; de Lagerberg, Julius, 1908-1920; de Lagerberg, Julius, 1921-1922; de Lagerberg, Julius; Delano, F. A.; Delano, Lyman; De Martino, Giacomo (Italian Ambassador); Denby, Edwin (Secretary, U.S. Navy); Denmark—Coin Cabinet; Dempsey & Carroll; Dennison Manufacturing Co.; Denzer & Nathan; de Pereira, Joaquin; Deschamps, Leon; Detroit, Mayor of; Detroit News; Devane, Joseph F. X. [Troy (NY) Chamber of Commerce]; Devreese, Godefroid; De Vinne Press; F. W. Devoe & C. T. Raynolds Co.; Dewing, Arthur S.; Dexter, Franklin B. (Mrs.) (Colonial Dames of America); de Yoanna, A.
  - Box 1.6.5 #26 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Diaz, Porfirio (Dictator, Mexico); Dickey, Charles D. (Mrs.).; Dickinson, Robert L.; Dieges & Clust; Dieudonne, A. (Bibliotheque Nationale); Dinsen & Co., Inc.; Distinguished Service Medal, 1917-1918; Dodge, Bayard (President, American University, Beirut); Dodge, Marcellus H.; Doelling, Louis; Dommerich, Otto L.; Dondero, A. H.; Dorr News Service; Dotti, Enrico; Charles A. Doubleday Books; R. F. Downing & Co.; Dows, David (Mrs.); Drennan, William (Drennan’s Vans); Dresden—Staatliche Muenzkabinett; Dresden Numismatic Society (Numismatisher Verein zu Dresden); Drew, Sydney; Drowne, L. S.; Drowne, Henry Russell, 1915-1917; Drowne, Henry Russell, 1918-1921
  - Box 1.6.6 #27 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Drummond, J. W.; Drury, Alfred; DuBois, Arthur E.; Debreuil, L. (French Embassy); Dudley, Mayo (Washington, D.C., Evening Star newspaper); Duffield, Franfurter G., 1915-1919 (Editor, The Numismatist); Duffield, Frankfurter G., 1922-1925 (Editor, The Numismatist); Duke University Press; Dumbadze, V. D.; Duncan, T. S. (St. Louis Numismatic Society); Dunham, Horace G.; Dunn, Roscoe L. (Librarian, Museum of Fine Arts, Boston); Dunscomb, S. Whitney (Jr.); Dutcher, George M.; E. P. Dutton & Co.
  - Box 1.6.7 #28 (ca. 1908-1931)
    E (unsorted)
  - Box 1.7.1 #29 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Eagle Almanac; Earhart, Frances E. (Librarian, Duluth Public Library); Earl, Douglas; Earl, Robert; Earle, Violet; Eastman, F. G.; Eastman Memorial Foundation; Eastwood, Eleanor; Eaton, Doane; Ebbets, Charles H.; Eberhardt, Frederick; Ebersole, F. J.; Les Editions Vitry; Editorial Mundo Latino (Madrid, Spain); Edmonds, Franklin S.; Edwards, Francis; Edwards, Franklin S.; Edwards, Joseph; Edwards, Virginia B.; Egger, Arnim (Egger Brothers); Ehlers, W. C.; Marc Eidlitz & Son; Eidlitz, Robert J.; Eidlitz, Robert J.
  - Box 1.7.2 #30 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Elco Gelatone Publishing Co.; Elder, Thomas.; Elderkin, George W.; Ellenhusen, Ulric.; Ellsworth, James; Elsworth Press, 1924-1926; Ely, Foster / Ely collection; Embler, Elizabeth D.; Emerson, Samuel (Mrs.); Emery, G. H.; Empedocles, G.; Emrick, M. W.; Encyclopedia Britannica; Endicott, F. Munroe; Engeli, A. (Director, Winterthur Numismatic Museum); B. Engessor Co.; Equitable Appraisal Co.; Equitable Trust Co. of New York; Erie Canal Centennial Commission; Ermitage Museum (Hermitage Museum); Ernst, Bernard M. L.; Essex Institute (Salem, Massachusetts); Ethical Cultural School; Euainetos decadrachm; Evans, Arthur (Sir); Evarts, Allan W.; Evening Post newspaper (New York, New York); Evening Sun newspaper (New York, New York); Arthur A. Everts Co.; Everett, Ethel (New York Times); Eyre, Louisa; Ezekiel, Henry C.
  - Box 1.7.3 #31 (ca. 1908-1931)
    F (unsorted)
  - Box 1.7.4 #32 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Faelten, Reinhold; Falls, DeWitt Clinton; Famous Players Lasky Corp; Fancher, F. R; Fang, Liang Luen (Chinese Consul); Farm and Fireside magazine; Farnham, Sally J; F. W. Faxton Co; Federal Reserve Bank—Cleveland; Federal Reserve Board—Washington, D.C; Federal Trade Commission; Feldman, Charles J; Ferguson, M; Ferris, Harlo; Field, William B. Osgood, 1910-1919; Field, William B. Osgood, 1920-1931; Fifth Avenue Coach Co; Finney, Howard (New York State Chamber of Commerce); Finnish legation; Finta, Alexander; Firestone, Archibald; Fish, Stuyvesant; Fisher, Robert.
  - Box 1.7.5 #33 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Flagg, Luther N; Flagler, Harry H; Flanagan, John; Fletcher, Frank; Fletcher, Henry; Flint, Charles R; Florange, Jules; Fock, Gustav; Foley, J; Folks, Homer (NY State Charities Aid Association); Forbes, H. R; Ford, James B; Fordyee, John A; Forrer, L. (Spink & Son); Forrestal, J. V; Fortier, J. (Mrs.); Foster, John W; Fowler, C. E; Franklin Institute; Franklin National Bank; Franklin Square Agency; Fraser, A. D; Fraser, James Earle; Frayne, Joseph; E. H. & A. C. Friedrichs Co; Freeman, Harley; French, Daniel Chester; French, Thomas E; French Institute in the United States; French Line; French Mint; Freres, Feuardent; Fresno County (CA) Public Library; Frew, Walter E; Frey, Albert R; Fuchs, Emil.
  - Box 1.7.6 #34 (ca. 1908-1931)
    G (unsorted)
  - Box 1.7.7 #35 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Gabrici, Ettore; Gaebler, H. (Kaiser Friedrich Museum); Gaettens, Richard; Gaines, Ruth (Huntington Free Library and Reading Room); Galbreath, C. B. (Ohio State Archaeological and Historical Society); Gallatin, Albert; Galli, Edoardo (Universita di Pisa); Galster, Georg (Copenhagen, Denmark); Galt, Caroline M; Gamber, J; Garcia Rico y Cia; Gardener, Percy (Ashmolean Museum); Garlick, A. J; Garrett, John W; Garrett, Robert; Garza, J. Sanchez; Gates, I. E; Gates, Milo H; Gatti, Guido; Gaunt, James; Gauthier-Villars & Co; George Junior Republic, 1920; William George’s Sons, booksellers; George Washington High School (New York, New York); George Washington Memorial Association; German Catholic Convention; Geuthner, Paul; Geyer, H. F; Giesecke, Walter; Gifford, C. S; Gies, A. C; Gilbert, Cass; Gilbert, S; Gilder, J. B; Gilhofer & Ranschburg; Giliberti, L. (Circolo Numismatica Napoletano); Gillett, George A; Gilliss, Walter.
  - Box 1.8.1 #36 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Gillingham, H. E., 1917-1920; Gillingham, H. E., 1923-1924; Gillingham, H. E., 1925; Gillingham, H. E., 1926; Gillingham, H. E., 1927; Gillingham, H. E., 1928; Gillingham, H. E., 1929; Gillingham, H. E., 1930; Gillingham, H. E., 1931; Gillingham, H. E., 1932.
  - Box 1.8.2 #37 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Gilmore, George L; Gilroy, Edward A. (Jr.); Ginori, Roberto V; Girolami, O; Glendining & Co., Ltd; Goddard, Charles; Goddard, George S. (Connecticut State Library); Goetz, Karl; Goessler, P. (Muenz und Medaillen); Goldsmith, Henry; Gombrich, Flora; Goodman, David C; Gordon, John; Gorham Co; Gough, John T. (New Orleans Times-Picayune); Gouch, W. A; Gould, Charles W; Gould, Edwin.
  - Box 1.8.3 #38 (ca. 1908-1931)
    W. R. Grace & Co; Joseph I. Grady Co; Graff, A. Stanley; Grafton & Co; Graham, Anderson, Probst & White, architects; Granberg, H. O; Grant, John; Grantley, _____ (Lord); Gravel, Ludger; Gray, H. A; Green, Elmer S; Green, Theodore F; Green, Thomas; Greene, Henry A; Greenough, John; Greenwich Safe Deposit Co; Greenwood, Mary M; Gregory, John; Grey, Viscount (British Ambassador); Gridley, Edward M; Grieshaber, Carl F; Griffith, Susan; Grimes, Frances; Grinnell, George Bird; Grinnell, William Morton; Grolier Club; Grose, S. W; Grossmann, I; Grosvenor Library (Buffalo, New York); Grouitch, Slavko Y. (Minister, Kingdom of the Serbs, Croats and Slovenes); Grover Cleveland Memorial Association; Guerrieri, G. (Director, Museo Provinciale S. Castromediano); Guerillot, M; Guernsey, Roscoe. (American Academy in Rome); Gunther Collection; Gunther, John Jacob; Gunther, C. Guthrie, J. A; Gutmann, Friedericus (Staatliches Munzkabinett Muenchen); Guttag, Julius / Guttag Brothers.
  - Box 1.8.4 #39 (ca. 1908-1931)
    H (unsorted)
  - Box 1.8.5 #40 (ca. 1908-1931)
  - Box 1.8.6 #41 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Haarer, John W; Habich, Georg (Director, Staatliches Munzkabinett Muenchen); Hachette et Cie; Hacienda y Credito Publico (Mexico City, Mexico); Hadden, Alexander M. / Hadden, John W; Hafner, Charles A; Hagan, Eero (Finnish Consul); Halls, F. S. (Director, State Museum, University of Washington); Halpern, S; Hamburger, Joseph; Hamburger, Leo; Hamilton, George L; Hamlin, Genevieve Karr; Hammacher, Schlemmer & Co; Hammond, Otis G. (New Hampshire Historical Society); Hanley, A. L; Hannan, E. E; Hansen, Harvey L. (Pacific Coast Numismatic Society); Hanson-Bennett Magazine Agency; Harbour, Jefferson L; Hardee, N. A; Harding, J. Horace; Harrassowitz, Otto; Harden, Edward; Hare, George J., photographer; Harriman, E. H. (Mrs.); Harrison, Alexander; Hart, Joseph; Hart, W. O; Hartman, Fred; Harvard Cooperative Society; Harvard University; Haseltine, J. W; Haskell, J. Amory; Hatch, L. J. (Mrs.); Haughton-Burke, Thomas A; Havemeyer, H. O. (Mrs.); Hawkes, McDougall (President, French Institute of the United States); Hayden, Horace E; Hazell’s Annual journal; Hazelton, Alan W.
  - Box 2.1.1 #42 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Heath, Walter C; Heaton, Augustus C; W. Heffer & Sons, Ltd; Heidel, W. A; Heinicke, Alfred; Heintz, Rene, J; Heliotypc Co; Hektograph Manufacturing and Duplicating Co; Helbing, Otto; Hemler, Alicia; Henderson, J. M; Hennegan-Bates Co; Henry, Philip W; Hensel, Bruckmann & Lorbacher; Herbert & Huesgen Co; B. Herder Book Co; Hermannsson, H. (Curator, Cornell University Library); Hermitage Museum; Herrick, F. M; Herring-Hall-Marvin Safe Co; Hess, Charles; Hesslein, William; Hewlett, Walter J; Heye, George Gustave (Museum of the American Indian); Hibbard, D. O. (YMCA Orange County, Florida); Hibbard Frederick C; Hidden, William E; Hiersemann, Karl W; Higgins, Frank (President, New York Numismatic Club); Hill, B. H. (American School of Classical Studies, Athens, Greece); Hill, George F. (British Museum); Hillhouse, J. T. B; Thomas Hindley & Sons; Hines, H. C; Hinton, Charles L; Hirschfeld, ______
  - Box 2.1.1 #43 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Hispanic Society of America; Historical Society of Pennsylvania; Historical Society of Western Pennsylvania; Hobart, R. H. Smith; Hoepli, Ulrico; Hoffman, Margaret; Hoffman, Samuel V; Holland, W. K. (AT&T); Holm, Frits; Holmes, William; Holstein, Otto; Homes News Press (New York, New York); Hood, Jennings (The Bailey, Banks & Biddle Co.) Hood, P. H; Hooper, Osman C; Hoopes, Thomas (Metropolitan Museum of Art); Hopkins, A. A; Hoppin, Joseph C. (Mrs.); Hossack, G. W; Housel, W. B; E. Howard & Co; Howard Memorial Library (New Orleans, Louisiana); Hoyt, John S; Hubbell, E. R; Hudson Bay Co; Hugendubel, Heinrich; The Huguenot Association of New Rochelle, New York
  - Box 2.1.3 #44 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Hulbert Bill; Hume & Walker; Hume, Edgar Erskine; Hummel, Ludwig; Hungarian Numismatic Society; Hunt, Joseph and Richard; Hunter, W. H; Huntington, Arabella; Huntington, Archer M., 1907-1910; Huntington, Archer M., 1911-1917; Huntington, Archer M., 1915-1918; Huntington, Archer M., 1919-1921; Huntington, Charles P; Huntington, Ford; Huntington, Henry E; Huston, George R; Hutchison, Joseph; Hutaf, A. W; Hyatt, Anna V; Hyde, E. Francis; Hyde, Frederick E; Hyde, James H.
  - Box 2.1.4 #45 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Ifould, W. H. (Sydney, Australia, Public Library); Ihrig, F. W; Illinois Watch Co; Illustration Engraving Co; Illyne, A; Imperial Brass Manufacturing Co; Imhoff, Charles H; Imperial Japanese Mint; Imperial Ottoman Museum (Istanbul, Turkey); Imperial War Museum of London; Indian Peace Medals; Indiana Historical Commission; Indiana State Library; Indiana University
  - Box 2.1.5 #46 (ca. 1908-1931)
    I (unsorted), Albert; Inglehart, D. S. (National Polo Pony Society, Inc.) Ingraham, Phoenix; Ingraham, Sara; Ingvall, A. P; Innes, Katherine (Director, Montclair Art Museum); Institut International de Cooperation Intellectuelle; Institute for Crippled & Disabled Men; Instituto Italiano d’Arte Grafiche; Instituto di Numismatica, Museo Nazionale delle Terme Diocleziane (Rome, Italy); Intelligencer Printing Co; International Art & Science Book Co; International Cable Registrations, Inc; International News Co; International Numismatic Congress (Brussels), 1910; International Studio; Iowa Masonic Library; Ireland, Gordon; Irish Setter Club of America; Irving, A. Duer; Italy—Royal Consul; Ives, Herbert E.
  - Box 2.1.6 #47 (ca. 1908-1931)
    William Jackson Co; Jacobs, Henry Barton; Jaegers, Albert; Jameson, J. Franklin; Jameson, R; Jaura, G; Thomas Jefferson Memorial Association; Jeffrey, Maud (Reference Librarian, Ohio State University); Jelliffe, Smith Ely; Jenny Lind Centennial Celebration; Jersey City (NJ Free Public Library; Jewelers’ Circular; Joannes, Francis. Y; Joannides, J. G; John Crera Library (Chicago, IL); Johns Hopkins University—Library; Johnson, B. G. (St. Louis Coin & Stamp Co.);Johnson, Franklin P. (University of Illinois); Johnson, George D; Johnson, Robert Underwood; Johnson & Johnson; Johnston, James G; Jones, M. B; Jones, Julia Zabriskie; Jones & Whitlock; Johnson, Stefano; Jordan, Thomas P; Journal of Economic and Business History; H. L. Judd Co; Judge, Thomas; Jusserand, Jean Jules (French Ambassador); Juszko, Jeno
  - Box 2.1.7 #48 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Contents
    K (unsorted); Kaiser Friedrich Museum (Berlin, Germany); Kohn, Otto H; Kambanis, Michel L; Kane, Joseph N; Kane Lodge Medal; Kansas City Public Library; Kansas State University; Kawamura, Gozo; Keck, M. H; Keene, A. F; Kegan, Trench, Trubner & Co; Kellad, K (unsorted); Daniel; ArnoldKeller & Co; Andrew H. Kellogg Co. (ANS brochure); Kelley, J. T; Kelly, Thomas Hughes; Kent, Henry W; Keppel, F. P; Khayat, Azeez; Kilenyi, Julio; Kilian, Georg (Staatliche Muenzsammlung Muenchen); King, Robert P; Klein, Adolph; Librarie C. Klincksieck; Knapp, Charles; William S. Koch & Son, bookbinders; Koch, Theodore (Librarian, Northwestern University Library); K. F. Koehlers Antiquarium (Leipzig, Germany); Kohler, Rudolph; Kohn, Albert M; Koga, Y. (Japanese Imperial Mint); Kohn, Albert M; Theodore A. Kohn & Son; Korper, Leo A. (Capital City Lumber Co.)
  - Box 2.2.1 #49 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Kungl. Biblioteket (Stockholm, Sweden); Kung. Vitterhets (Stockholm, Sweden); Kusterer, Leonard; Kunz, George, 1906-1915; Kunz, George, 1916-1919; Kunz, George, 1920-1925
  - Box 2.2.2 #50 (ca. 1908-1931)
    L (unsorted); Laborie, Jean; Laessle, Albert; Lafayette Day National Committee. Lafayette Medal; Laffranchi, Lodovico; Lake County Historical Society (Chicago, IL); Lambert, J. B; Lambert Samuel W.
  - Box 2.2.3 #51 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Lancaster Press; Lance, G. C; Landa E; Langdale, W. G; Landon, E. H; Langdon, Webster F; Langdon, William Chauncey; Lange, Paul M; Langenheim, F. D. (Numismatic and Antiquarian Society of Philadelphia); Langton, John J. P; Lapointe, L. La Revue Moderne; Laughlin, Randolph Charles E. Lauriat Co., booksellers; Lawless, Elmer; Lawrence, Frederick George; Lawrence, George Alfred; Lawrence, Richard Hoe; Lay, Charles (Municipal Art Society of New York)
  - Box 2.2.4 #52 (ca. 1908-1931)
    A. B. Leach & Co; LeBlanc, J. F; Lederer, Philip; Ledon, Luis Castillo (Director, Museo National de Arqueologia, Mexico City, Mexico); Leeper, Roxa; Leijonhufvud, Sigrid; Leominster Public Library (Leominster, MA); Leon, Maurice; Lerando, Leon Z; Lewis, Eugene; Leroux, Ernest; LeRoy, Louis C; Lester, Henry M; Leve, A. Atlas; Levenson, J; Levis, Howard C; Lewis, John F. (Pennsylvania Academy of Fine Arts); C. F. Libbie & Co; Librairie Paul Ritti; Library Bureau, 1908-1923; Library Bureau, 1924-1927; Library of Congress, 1912-1928; Library of Congress, 1931-1932; Libreria di Cultura (Rome, Italy); Library Journal
  - Box 2.2.5 #53 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Lieber, Carl H. (Art Association of Indianapolis, Indiana).; Liebert, Gaston (French Consul).; Lillard, R. W. (Associated Dry Goods Corp.).; Lincoln, Frederick W.; Lincoln Memorial Commission.; Lindheim, Norvin R.; Ling, Harry L.; J. B. Lippincott Co.; Liveright, Frank. J.; Livingston, L. A.; Lloyd, Allan G.; Lloyd, A. H.; Lober, George J.; Loeb, James.; Loeb, Morris (Mrs.).; Loeb, Morris; Frederick Loeser & Co.; Loftus Brothers; B. Login & Son.; Corporation of London.; London Mint.; Long Island Historical Society.; Longman, Evelyn Beatrice.; Lorentz, Alfred.; Lorenzani, A. E.; Los Angeles Public Library; Loubat, Duke of.; Louisiana Historical Society.; Low, Lyman H.; W. H. Lowdermilk & Co., rare book dealers.; Lowell A. L. (Harvard University); Lowenstam, B. G.; Lownes, M. E.; Lucas, F. A. (American Museum of Natural History).; Luce, Stephen.; Lyman, R. H. (The World newspaper).; Lynch, James A. Lynge, Herman; Lyon, Bert.
  - Box 2.2.6 #54 (ca. 1908-1931)
    M (unsorted)
  - Box 2.3.1 #55 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Mabbott, Thomas O.; James MacDonald Co., bookbinder.; MacDonald, Lillian M.; MacDonald & Maier.; MacDonald, George; Macdonald, Lucy W. (Secretary, Royal Society of Miniature Painters); MacIlvaine, J. B. S.; MacKenzie, Thomas R.; MacLean, J. Arthur (Art Institute of Chicago); Macallister, James J.; MacMahon, R. C.; Macmillan Co.; MacMonnies, Frederick; MacNeil, Hermon A.; Magoffin, Ralph V. D. (New York University); Madlener, A. F.; Maemple, M. C.; Magyar Numismatikai Tarsulat (Budapest, Hungary); Maine Historical Society; Maltry, M.; Maly, Franz.; Manley, Herbert D.; Mann, Earl S.; Manning, C. (Committee on Foreign Medals); Manning, James H.; Manship, Paul.; Manuel II (King of Portugal).; Marburg, Theodore.; March, Peyton (U.S. War Department).; Marcotte, Abbe Leon.; Margetts, N. E. (U.S. War Department).; Mariani, Lucio.; Markert, Karl.; Marlier, George F.; Markus, Charles.; Marquand, Allan (Princeton University).; Marshall, Sue.; Marshall, Rudolf.; Marshall, Vause W.; Marshalltown (IA) Public Library.; Martin, George Castor.; Martin, Laura Grinnell.; Martin, Newell.; Martin, W. R. (Librarian, Hispanic Society of America).; Marvin, Elizabeth E.; Marvin, Selden E. (Jenny Lind Centennial Celebration).; T. R. Marvin & Son.; Maryowski, T. (Polish Consulate).; Marx, Jacob.; Mason, W. E. (Metropolitan Museum of Art).; Massachusetts Historical Society.; Massachusetts Society for Promoting Agriculture.; Massachusetts, State Library of.; Massachusetts Treasury Department.; Matalene, Henry W.; Matthews, Brander (Chancellor, American Academy of Arts & Letters).; Maurice, M.; Maverick, W. C.; Mavrogordato, J.; Maxwell, J. S.; Mayer and Muller (Nomisma journal).; Mazerolle, Fernand.
  - Box 2.3.2 #56 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Mc (unsorted).; McAllister, Martin D.; McCall, D. H.; H. W. McCandless & Co.; McCaulley, Mariana.; A. C. McClurg & Co., booksellers.; McCormick, Harry T.; McCoy, Lizzie, T.; McCraven, J. M. P.; McGraw-Hill Co.; McHugh, Edward J.; McKenna, M. L.; McKenzie, Alex.; McKenzie, R. Tait (University of Pennsylvania).; McKinley Birthplace Memorial Association.; McKim, Mead & White (American Academy / Arts & Letters).; McLachlan, R. W.; McLane, Kate M.; McLaughlin, P. J.; McMahon, B. B.
  - Box 2.3.3 #57 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Meagher, Margaret C.; Means, Philip A.; The Mediaeval Academy of America.; Medallic Art Co.; Medallic Art Co.; Medallic Art Co.; Medina, Jose.; Meehan, George.; Meeker, H. E.; Mehl, B. Max.; Mehren, E. J. (McGraw-Hill Co.); Meissner, Amelia (Educational Museum Curator, St. Louis Board of Education).; Mellen, C. S.; Mellon, Andrew (U.S. Treasury Secretary).; Mercantile Bank of the Americas.; Merchants’ Association of New York.; C. & G. Merriam Co.; Merritt, Ferriss P.; Merzbacher, E. Metropolitan Museum of Art. Menconi Brothers. Meuss, Hans.
  - Box 2.3.4 #58 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Miami University.; Milbank, A. G.; Milbank, Samuel R.; Miller, C. V.; Miller, George N.; Miller, Hoyt.; Miller, Thomas S. (NY Numismatic Club).; Miller, William J.; Milliken, C. F. (Ontario County Historical Society).; Mills, A. G.; Mills, William C. (Curator, Ohio State Archaeological and Historical Society).; Milmine, C. E.; Minnesota Historical Society.; Mirone, Salvatore.; Mitchell, William.
  - Box 2.3.5 #59 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Moisil, Constantine (Societatea Numismatica Romana).; Moore, Charles (U.S. Commission of Fine Arts).; Moore, H. C.; Moore, J. Clark.; Moore, S. L.; Morgan, Caroline L.; Morgan, Edward B.; Morgan, J. Pierpont (Morgan Library).; Morgan, William F.; Morgenthau, M. L.; Morison, Horace (Society of the Cincinnati).; Morris, Joseph L.; Morris, Lewis R.; Morris, Nathalie Bailey.; Morrison, Norah F.; Morse, C. H.; Morse, Ten Broeck.; Mosley, Eleanor.; Mott-Smith, May.; Mountbatton, _______.; Mouroux, Anie.; Moynihan F.; Mulliner, W.; Mueller, Johannes.; Municipal Reference Library (ANS military exhibition).; Munsterberger, R. (Kunsthistorisches Museum Wein).; Murray, James.; Museu Nacionale Rio de Janeiro.; Museum of the American Indian.; Museum of Fine Arts, Boston.; Muskogee (OK) Public Library.
  - Box 2.3.6 #60 (ca. 1908-1931)
    N (unsorted).
  - Box 2.3.7 #61 (ca. 1908-1931)
    Nachf, Otto.; Nagai, S. (Director, Imperial Mint of Japan).; Naon, Romulo (Argentinean Consulate).; Nathan, Maud.; National Academy of Art.; National Academy of Design.; National Arts Club.; National Bank of South Africa.; National Cyclopedia of American Biography.; National District Telegraph Co.; National Geographic Society.; National Institute of Arts and Letters.; National Polo Pony Society.; National Press Club.; National Sculpture Society catalog—acknowledgements.; National Union List of Serials.; Navarro, J. C. Olina.; Neandross, Sigird.; Negri, Ottavio.; Neil, Will.; Neilson, Howard S.; Nelles, E.; Nelson, Peter (University of the State of New York).; New England Society of New York City.; New England Steamship Co.; New Jersey Historical Society.
  - Box 2.4.1 #62 (ca. 1908-1931)
    New York Central Railroad.; New York City—Board of Education.; New York City—Internal Revenue.; New York City—Parks.; New York City—Public Works.; New York City—Tercentenary.; New York City—Water Supply.; New York Genealogical and Biographical Society.; New York Historical Society.; New York Library Club.; New York Life Insurance and Trust Co.; New York, New Haven & Hudson Railroad.; New York Numismatic Club.; New York Public Library.; New York Society Library.; New York Special Libraries Association.; New York State Library.; New York Telephone Co.; New York Times.; New York University.; New York World.; Newark Museum Association.; Newark Paper Box Co.; Newark Public Library.; Newcomb, Howard R.; Newcomb, Waldo.;; Box 2.4.2 #63;; Newell, Adra.; Newell, Edward T., 1905-1914.; Newell, Edward T., 1915-1919.; Newell, Edward T., 1920-1941.; Newell, Edward T., assorted dates.; Newell, Edward T., assorted dates.; Newman, Allan G.; Newman, J. F.; Newspapers.
  - Box 2.4.3 #64 (Ca. 1908-1931)
    University of Beruit).; Nielsen, N. C.; Nijhoff, Martinus, bookseller.; Nissim, Judah A. S.; Noe, Sydney P., 1915.; Nocq, Henri.; Noetzel, Fred W.; Nomisma.; Noorian, Daniel Z.; Noorian, J. Nicodemi, G. (Medagliere Milanese).; Nicolletti, Vincent A.; Nickoley, Edward F. (President, Zado.; A. B. Nordiska, booksellers.; Nordman, C. A.; Norlind, Tobias.; The Norman, Remington Co.; Norsted & Soner.; Novelli, James.; Numismatische Gesellschaft (Vienna, Austria).; Numismatic Society of India.; Nystrom & Co.
  - Box 2.4.4 #65 (Ca. 1908-1931)